like Hey I'll tell you one thing
como Oye te digo una cosa no ha dicho
this guy hasn't said a [ __ ] word What do you
una [__] palabrota este tío Qué te
think eye eh What a great program that was eh it's
parece ojo eh Vaya programón ha sido eh
awesome I mean we haven't called
está acojonante O sea no hemos llamado
anyone a son of a [ __ ] I mean neither disgusting to
hijop [__] a nadie o sea ni ni asqueroso
errejón nor slobber to the glasses that
a errejón ni ni baboso al al gafas ese
disgusting one I have been I have been measured
asqueroso he sido he sido comedido
because [ __ ] you guys are just starting I don't want
porque [__] estáis empezando no quiero
you to get screwed here the second V No
que os que os jodan aquí el segundo V No
if it's Javi who's J it's his channel I
si es a Javi al que le J es su canal yo
'm here to
estoy aquí para para el cachondeo al que
have fun the one who's getting screwed is him he tells me we don't do it you put it on your channel he gave a dick I put it on my channel Dani me nor I normally when I'm with Fran live I'm usually with her with the little drop here of sweat on my forehead and I say oh
gotita aquí de sudo en la frente y digo
my god after what a mess
madre mía después de la que se Lio La
Last week I brought myself remember do you
semana pasada me traigo acuerdas te
remember one day we were talking
acuerdas un día que estábamos hablando
with trium about I don't know what And I started
con trium de no sé qué Y me puse a
talking about ábalos and the other and the
hablar de de ábalos y del otro y del
other and I started to [ __ ] myself and you had it
otro y me empecé a [__] en y lo tuviste
no but what it was was I had to
que no pero qué lo que fue fue tuve que
remember directly because it's that
recordar directo porque es que se le se
Fran's wheel went directly
le fue el volante a Fran directamente
but in the middle of live with 18,000 people
pero en pleno directo con 18000 personas
eh And he went off the wheel and he started to
eh Y se le fue el volante y empezó a
started accusing crimes to I don't know who I do
empezó a imputarle delitos a no sé quién
n't know how many dead the whole family was mentioned
a no sé cuánto muerto se mentó toda la
Yo [ __ ] they banned the
familia Yo cabrón os lo banearon el
video then or he couldn't take it he cut it all
vídeo luego o no aguantó lo cortó todo
not everything I didn't cut a piece because
no todo no corté un trozo porque se puso
Fran went a a I think it was against a prosecutor
Fran a a creo que era contra una fiscal
or a judge or something like that I say it wasn't
o una jueza o algo así que digo no era
against this fat son of a [ __ ] the one who
contra la gorda hija de [__] esta la que
was in the fat one that I named after
estaba en la gorda que le puse el nombre
the cow do you remember I have a cow
de la vaca te acuerdas yo tengo una vaca
called Pam and I named her and
que se llama pam y le puse el nombre y
then I wrote an article in El
entonces me escribí un artículo en el
País Don't remember that I wrote an
país No te acuerdas que me escribí un
article saying that and it was from
artículo diciendo queo y era a partir de
there with Ábalos I impaled it with
ahí con con el ábalos yo lo empal con
everything and I ended up talking about
todo y terminé hablando de
Ábalos talking about
ábalos hablando
the triumph freaking out Dani here is your
el el triun flipando Dani aquí tienes tu
house it has been a pleasure man I really
casa ha sido todo un placer tío tenía
wanted to I promise you that  haa
muchas ganas Te lo prometo que haa
thank you very much thank you very much
muchas gracias muchas gracias muchas
thank you for coming because [ __ ]
gracias por venir porque [__]
eh I'm sure they're calling you from all
eh seguro que te está llamando de todos
sides but but no I don't give them And
los lados pero pero no no los doy Y
also I'm telling you I have a
además ya te lo digo tengo una agencia
representation agency that I find very
de representación que me hace mucha
funny no but when you move a
gracia no pero cuando ya mueves unos
certain number yes it's true I would
ciertos números sí que es verdad Me
like them to invite me to cco or 10
gustaría me me invitan a cco o 10
podcasts a week but no no because it wouldn't be the
podcast a la semana pero no no porque no
same obviously you lose Of course
sería lo mismo obviamente pierde Claro
if you go to everything you lose So I'd be
si vas a todo pierde la Entonces yo
delighted and we're going to give you all the advertising you
encantado y le vamos a dar toda la publi
want and and tell and And if we have to come
que queráis y y contar y Y si hay que
back and we give you the political promotion
volver y os damos la promoción política
or I go there for a week to see the bugs
o me voy una semana ahí a ver los bichos
with Fran or something, well that's what you
con Fran o una cosa pues eso eso te lo
could do here Ask
podías hacer aquí Pregúntale
Ay yesterday yesterday I had lunch with my representative
a Ay ayer ayer comí con mi representante
And obviously I decide where I go and where I do
Y obviamente yo decido dónde voy y dónde
n't go I have it but I told him I haven't
no voy lo tengo pero le dije yo no he
asked if I could come with you
preguntado si podía venir con vosotros
Javi I think I answered you right away
Javi creo que te contesté al momento
also without I answered you I said [ __ ] yes
además sin yo te contesté dije [__] sí
I feel like it could be fun and yesterday
me apetece puede ser divertido y ayer
eating with Luis with my
comiendo con con Luis con mi
representative He told me what you
representante Él me decía tú lo que
have because I have been three three or four
tienes porque yo llevo tres tres o cuat
years without taking a vacation okay  because
años sin hacer vacaciones vale porque yo
then in the end here well eh of course I don't I don't
luego al final aquí pues eh claro Yo no
have I have six
yo no tengo yo tengo seis perros
rescued dogs here and everything plus everything that I
rescatados aquí y todo más todo lo que
rescued you know you can't because I
rescat tú sabes que no puedes porque
have the wolf the cork dog the
tengo el lobo el canec corcho el bitbol
rescued fighting dog I have all kinds
de pelea rescatado un tengo de todo tipo
of And then stop leaving the
de de Y entonces dejar dejar los
animals with with anyone you don't know I
animales con con cualquiera no sabes o
mean it's you have that those of us who have
sea es tienes que los que tenemos
animals are you always worried you're
animales estás preocupado siempre estás
always worried we stop doing a
siempre preocupado dejamos de hacer 1
million things for the animals and
millones de cosas por los animales y
like I've been like this my whole life Right now
como yo llevo toda mi vida así Ahora
I live alone with my dogs I mean
mismo yo vivo solo con mis perros o sea
I can't stand people I'm a bit
yo no soporto a la gente Soy un poco
like you my moment right now if I
como tú yo mi momento ahora mismo si
looked over there I have the relaxation music on
mirara para allá tengo puesta la música
and there are four dogs
de relajación y están cuatro perros
sleeping on the couch and two outside in
dormiendo en el sofá y dos por fuera en
the garden okay And now I do the shift I have to
el jardín vale Y ahora hago el turno les
feed them and what do I get but
tengo que dar de comer y que saco pero
talking to him he told me go for a week
hablando con él me decía vete una semana
with Fran there to record videos and do you go on
con Fran allí a grabar vídeos y haces
vacation I say dude the truth is it
vacaciones digo bu tío la verdad que
could be fun but I don't know in
puede ser divertido pero no sé yo en
a few days here deí Look Ask
unos días aquí deí Mira Pregúntale a
Yusso who has been here that people
yuso que ha estado aquí que la gente
don't Listen to me I said no I Because
no Escúchame yo decía que no yo Porque
I Also I have a  cron no s
yo Además tengo enfermedad de cron no s
twice I've gone in years there is a
dos veces he ido es años hay vuelo
direct flight from Madrid can I go alone yes yes yes yes there is a
directo desde Madrid yo puedo ir solo sí
direct flight there is a
sí sí sí ya hay vuelo directo hay vuelo
direct flight already from Madrid Yes there is a
directo ya desde Madrid Sí hay vuelo
direct flight from Madrid come on let's go
directo desde Madrid venga vamos
Hold my drink for me damn Hold my drink for me
Aguántame el cubata [__] Aguántame el
Dani go man and join him in
cubata Dani ve tío y lo acompañas en la
jail listen to me Here I have the
cárcel a escúchame Aquí tengo el
calendar you don't know me much and listen to me
calendario poco me conocéis y escúchame
the experience is brutal the
la experiencia es brutal la experiencia
brutal experience danoy if I'm not in
brutal danoy si no estoy en la
jail well let him accompany you damn me let him
cárcel bueno que te acompañe [__] yo que
defend you I have no problem
te defienda no tengo problema
yoem fech You put the date April of
yoem fech Tú pon la fecha abril di
April AB yeah I live here alone I
abril AB a si es que yo vivo aquí solo
live with Paloma and with 300 bugs
vivo con Paloma y con 300 bichos
watch out okay listen to me I'm coming with my
ojo vale escúchame me vengo con mi
representative and a camera and we'll make a
representante y una cámara y la liamos
mess watch out
parda ojo
good Spaniards and PR Okay so
ojo españoles de bien y PR Vale pues ya
April is here and progress whenever you want
está abril y progres de cuando quieras
confirm the dates Dani is vacating He's going
confirmas las fechas Dani desocupa Se va
with Frank to Thailand let's vacate
con Frank a Tailandia vamos a desocupar
the doggy deer from here the son of a [ __ ] we
al ciervo perrito de aquí al hijo [__]
take out esc Fran I'll bring you my cap well I'll
sacamos esc Fran Te llevaré mi gorra
put it over here okay handsome How
pues la colocaré por aquí vale guapo Qué
handsome I'll bring  my cap well nothing we'll
guapo llevaré mi gorra pues nada nos
talk privately in April you have me
hablamos por privado en abril me tienes
in Thailand well that's it [ __ ] [ __ ]
en Tailandia pues ya está [__] [__]
Look there it is more is more if God wants
Mira ya est es más es más si Dios quiere
we can do a podcast there again
podemos volver a hacer un podcast allí
the two of us and we drop the political bomb
los dos y lanzamos la bomba política
damn Javi you have to catch a plane watch out
[__] Javi te tienes que [__] un avión
eh watch out you have to catch a plane and
ojo eh ojo tienes que [__] un avión y
also it depends on the reaction Fran as it
además depende de la reacción Fran como
catches me in Thailand maybe you stay you
me pilla en Tailandia igual te quedas te
stay here of
quedas aquí
course and I register there with you
claro y me empadrono allí contigo
also we have to see if
también hay que también hay que ver si
Fran makes it to April because of course in
Fran llega a abril porque claro por
between there are some There are some other
medio hay alguna Hay algún que otro
potholes okay they're going to put you in jail for a
bache vale van a meter en la cárcel un
month I have good lawyers if you
mes yo tengo buenos abogados si
need little joke count on my lawyers
necesitas poca broma cuenta con mis abog
no but it's that here here here you don't know what it's like
no pero es que aquí aquí aquí no sabes
here it's very different very very very
cómo es aquí es muy diferente muy muy
different very different there is one it's
muy diferente muy diferente hay una es
Thailand you have to accept the rules That's why I
Tailandia hay que aceptar las reglas Yo
said that I get whatever I get
por eso que he dicho que me toque lo que
I accept It's that I live here it's like that okay
me toque yo acepto Es que yo vivo aquí
wait no I didn't cut yet
es así vale espera no no corté todavía
what I want let's make an advance
que quiero vamos a hacer un anticipo
to give you guys a hard time with this I'm going to record
para daros caña al de esto voy a grabar
like this with your permission to announce it
así con vuestro permiso para anunciarlo
okay I didn't cut Eh Good afternoon family
vale no corté Eh Buenas tardes familia
news I'm here with  My friend Fran and
novedad estoy aquí con mi amigo Fran y
my friend Javi here you have them both we have
mi amigo Javi aquí los tenéis a los dos
just recorded the podcast for his
acabamos de grabar el podcast para su
channel and we have just announced that the
canal y acabamos de anunciar que el
menda herenda in April is going for a week
menda herenda en abril se va una semana
from the jungle to Thailand is that right
con Fran de la jungla a Tailandia es así
Fran or not
Fran o no
Yes because I have to vacate some rats
Sí porque tengo que desocupar unas ratas
from
de
here so nothing to
aquí entonces pues nada que me las
vacate them one is called Pablo the
desocupe se llama una se llama Pablo la
other is called
otra se llama
Íñigo and the other is called Ire they call her
Íñigo y la otra se llama Ire le llaman
Ire I don't know what it is but come on we have to
Ire No sé lo que es pero vamos hay que
vacate well you know in April
desocuparas pues ya sabéis en abril
second part of the podcast from
segunda parte del podcast desde
Thailand come suck it up reds
Tailandia venga a mamarla rojos
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Can you send this link because my
podem enviar este enlace porque mi
representative wrote to me a while ago he
representante me ha escrito hace un rato
says How is the podcast going I'm going to
me dice Cómo va el podcast le voy a
send it Just this video You'll see you the one who
enviar Solo este vídeo Ya verás tú la
hears nothing Hey a pleasure really it's
que oye nada Oye un placer en serio está
very fun the pleasure is our
muy divertido el placer es nuestro
spectacular Well it's time to say goodbye now it's time to say
espectacular Bueno hay que despedirse ya
goodbye with the Jesusito of my
hay que despedirse con el Jesusito de mi
life you are a child like me that's why I
vida eres niño como yo por eso que te
love you so much that I give you my heart
quiero tanto que te doy mi corazón
take it take it it's yours and mine
tómalo tómalo tuyo es y mío
not my goodness and
no madre mía e
the my goodness is Cristiano's  This is from
el madre mía es de Cristiano esto es de
Cristiano Jesus, my little Jesus, my life like me That's why I
Cristiano Jesusito de mi vida como yo
love you so much that I have my
Por eso te quiero tanto que tey mi
heart, take it, take it, you, it's my mother, my
corazón tómalo tómalo tu yo es madre mía
mother,
madre
a hug, Dani. Hey, have a good time, Fran.
mía un abrazo Dani Oye pasarlo bien Fran
See you in April, write to me. Pass it on. Pass him
nos vemos en abril escríbeme Pásale
my phone number and we'll write to each other on
Pásale mi teléfono y nos escribimos por
WhatsApp. Fran, come on.
WhatsApp Fran venga